The Magic Channel is starting!
Yeah!
- Yeah! This is it! It's high, you know?
Yes, this is the Volta Ring project!
- Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Just so you know, it's not high!
No, it's not!
Today is a magic party!
Yeah!
Hey, it's not the same at all, just different! Voltaire and...
Is it?
I don't know.
Don't snap at me like that.
- Can I report one thing? Yes, sir.
- Yuma's time is up.
Oh, no.
- Let's stop.
- He just did it.
- Didn't anyone notice?
- No, sorry
- No, I'm sorry, it's just normal, you know.
- Let's just take it easy.
- We don't need you.
- Maybe we'll start that way.
- I might start that way.
- Okay, yakiniku.
- Okay, now, barbecue.
- Yes!
- We're clearing the 10th floor of the house.
- I'll give you 15 more minutes to talk here.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- And, um, afterwards...
- And, uh, afterwards, we'll have a lot of talking.
- No, after that, we'll do the yakiniku video.
- Video.
- That's new.
- That's good.
- That's what I want to do.
- Okay, well, let's clear the next one.
- Once we're through, once we're through.
- Theory's clear. I'm sure it's clear.
- You.
- I've already cleared it.
- You're not here today, Kevin.
- I was wondering who's going to take Kevin's spot.
- Yeah, theory's important.
- What?
- Well, let's give it a shot.
- Well, let's give it a shot. - You call it a theory already?
- And there's rust.
- We're definitely not supposed to do that.
- There's a chorus, too.
- You're never allowed to do that.
- It's not allowed anyway.
- Let's do "Theory" one more time.
- Let's do Theory.
- Theory. Theory.
- Okay, whatever.
- Start.
- The first one who says it, I'm gonna pinkie chop him as hard as I can.
- Pinky-poke me, I'll be gentle
Psi-Po, you're in command
Ghosts and Goblins
It's been a while.
It's hard to do
Oh fill in this distance
If there's a trail, can't you shake your hand
If it were invisible
Just one
Well, well, well, well, well
I can't help it
I still want praise for saying it
I just remembered... we're supposed to sing this out.
So we'll do it in the northern order today?
Wait a minute.
Oh, I see.
Can we go?
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Let's go once.
But in the order that they were laid out on the street.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's start with "Music.
Let's go in that north order, seriously, seriously
Kita-jun, Kita-jun, Kita-jun
Pushipode, hold my hand
Osooba wa nai yo yo
Oh, I'll fill this distance
Can't we do it like that
If it's something invisible
Just one thing
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
Because you're here
You make me look so dazzling
You make me look so cool
No, that song.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.Wow, wait.
If it's the style without the crazy feelings.
Oooooh!
Why oh why are you with me?
Wait a minute now grandpa
Wait a minute!
Hey!
You made it to the top!
Yeah, we really made it.
Right here.
You three went here together.
Why? Why? Why?
We've done it three times!
That's the third time!
I've never seen a barbecue like this in the beginning.
First time.
It was the first time!
The way you were so happy at the end.
Can you make reservations for yakiniku?
We've only done it twice.
If we're going to leave the studio soon like this...
You're right, make a reservation.
I'll pack my stuff.
Okay?
Money, money, money...
Let's start with the singers.
I guess so.
This distance.
I can make it.
I'll do it one more time like a normal person.
Don't even think about it.
Wrap it up.
I'm done. No more subjects.
Feeling.
I didn't do feeling once.
I'm relying a little too much on the theme.
No more of the same.
I'm going to start the music with feeling.
I hope you're feeling it.
Come here.
I'll get it.
You're not so tight.
That's the distance
One more time.
Here we go.
I can't be bothered
What you don't see
Maybe we can see it.
Oh, shit.
It's so invisible.
I think it's good.
It's true.
It's the same.
You're a master.
We're the same, too.
Cotton.
I bought it.
It's good, but it's not that good.
Try it later.
I bought a pair, but it was a mistake.
They sold them.
They're not here.
Don't sell them now.
I didn't sell them.
I don't care if you sell them.
I don't care if you come in with a different one.
Why are we rehearsing today?
I'm gonna drink some water.
That's what we're gonna do.
I'm not drinking.
You're drinking less than this guy.
You're drinking more than him.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't know.
More than him.
I think I'm drinking right now.
Start.
Masaoka, I'm all for it.
Hokuto, have fun.
Kyomoto, I drank.
Kyomoto. It's sweet, so I'll live.
Inoue By the way, how much do you drink every day?
Takahashi I drank at least 2 liters every day.
Takahashi I drink...
Takahashi Oh, I drank at least 2 liters every day.
We drank 2 liters together.
Matsukura Then I can't do it!
I drank the same kind.
Kyomoto, I can't do it then.
Inoue Something today...
Inoue I always buy these, Ethan.
Ethan Sakuma This one and the one we drink at home.
Kyomoto: I'm sure we'll end up with...
Kyomoto, will you be okay? I'm sure Kyoumoto will be in a funk at the end... and leave.
Inogari-san... you call it "unglazed red bean paste".
It's called "unglazed sweet bean paste".
I asked for it earlier.
I saw it earlier.
Oh no...
I can't see it without starting the music.I can't see this without starting the music like this in the back.
I think I might have seen it.
I'm so excited about this.
Let's do that.
A lot of people go to the bathroom during rehearsal.
Wow.
What?
A lot of people don't go to the bathroom during rehearsal.
I'll have to try it.
You never know.
We're about the same, aren't we?
Let's do it once.
Let's start the music.
Takahashi, really? Inoue Good idea.
Inokari No, let's just go to the finish line.
Takahashi I don't want to go get it. Inoue No, I've already done it once.
Takahashi No, you can go three times a day.
Takahashi, you! Inoue You're taking it away from me!
Takahashi, you're an idol. You shouldn't push around.
Inokari, what's your problem?
Takahashi!
Inogari, what are you if we're in a group together?
Takahashi I'm a geisha.
Inoue A geisha?
Inoue Geishas are girly.
Takahashi, are you blushing?
Inogari: Red face?
Inogari, your face is attracting attention.
Inogari, stop blushing from all the attention.
Inokari, you're cute.
Takahashi! No, no, no...
No!
Inogari! Wait! No!
Takahashi... Long arms...
Inoue Long arms?
Inogari I'm sure I'm cute.
Inogari And you can even measure them!
Takahashi That's true.
Inokari That's right.
Inokari That's for sure.
Takahashi: So if you measure it and it's too short...
Takahashi: Why did you get a new one? I'll be like "Why did you get a new one?
Inogari I can do it.
Reina, you're really scary!
Rinning, Singin, change!
Rinning, I'm verifying it too.
Rinning, I'm really long.
Daiko, put your backs together.
Rein-Ya, this is bad. I think I'm blind.
Rein-Ya, stretch B.
Rinya, are your shoulders aligned?
Rin Ning, that's why our shoulders are together.
Yabana Oh, the same?
RinNing, but your shoulders are right here.
RinNing, maybe it's more about sex.
RinNing, maybe if you do it with one hand...
RinNing, maybe it's here.
Ms. Konno, I don't think that's possible.
Ms. Ukisho, Mr. Abe.
Iwamoto-san, do you mean big?
Iwamoto, you are really wide here.
Iwamoto-san, shoulder width?
Iwamoto-san, sorry guys.
Iwamoto-san, I hear you.
Iwamoto-san, you're bad.
Iwamoto san, subject.
Daisuke Sakuma, let me get this straight.
Daisuke Sakuma, in order of how strongly you think dinosaurs lived.
Iwamoto-san, wow!
Daisuke Sakuma, I like it!
Daisuke Sakuma, you can do it!
Takahashi: No, we've already decided on the first and second.
Inokari... No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Inogari... Dinosaurs were alive...
Inoue That's crazy!
Inoue... dinosaurs are alive?
Inoue It's not that there's a dinosaur...
Inogari That's why I think so strongly about it
Inoue I mean strongly... that the dinosaurs were alive?
Inogari Some people say they're not alive...
Inoue But you know... they have bones...
Inokari Even if it has bones...
Inoue Well, then... it was alive...
Inoue No, no, no, no, no, no, no, not aliens
Inokari I strongly believe there are aliens
Inokari He's the one who strongly believes in aliens, so go!
Inoue Honestly, I'm troubled by it
Inogari No, look at the person
Inogari I don't think so any more than this guy...
Inokari Seriously, now you're getting it right...
Inoue But you know what I mean... aliens...
Inoue What you're saying...
Inokari Who's an alien?
Inoue They exist, don't they?
Inokari They exist!
Inoue Did you say they're here?Inoue: You're here, didn't you say?
Inokari... A gorilla and an alien...
Inokari Then you've infiltrated Bodie's.
Inoue 29
Inoue 30
Inoue That's crazy!
Inoue... Today...
- No, no, no, no! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Come on!
- I'm out! Come on!
- I strongly believe there are aliens.
- You think so, don't you?
- You're thinking it, aren't you?
- I thought you were next.
- No, no, no, no!
- You're not saying much, are you?
- I really think you're an alien, Hame-kun.
- I don't want to give you roses.
- I really don't want to tell on Hamekun.
- I really don't want to give it away.
- I really don't want to tell anyone. I'm the one who infiltrated the Baggies.
- It's me!
- Oh, wait, no, not the alien.
- Let's say I'm out.
- Okay.
- Who was going next?
- Me!
- Me! Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
- I thought so, too.
- I have no choice.
- I didn't expect it to be St. Night.
- I thought I'd be next.
- I thought I'd be second to you.
- How can you even think about it?
- I'm not sure I'm a fan of that.
- Then no more yakiniku.
- No more yakiniku.
- Yakiniku.
- Yes.
- No, it's not.
- What's the next stage?
- Not a promise...
- Ramen
- Ramen.
- It's totally fine.
- Ramen noodles.
- It's ramen, but it's ramen, so what's the big deal?
- I'm always banging on the door.
- Ramen's fine.
- Now...
- Okay, for the 20th time.
- Oh, really?
- Really?
- Ramen good?
- Say yes.
- Let's go.
- Oh, 20...
- Ten more to go and then we'll get ramen.
- That's too much!
- How many times, how many times, how many times?
- Then I want to go for ramen!
- I want to go.
- I want to go to ramen... - No, I don't want to go to ramen.
- That's crazy!
- That's fast! That's crazy fast!
- You guys!
- Hey, guys!
- Let's do that again.
- You guys are wearing a lot of jewelry, right?
- I was going to say "wow", but...
- But now everyone's wearing them.
- How much jewelry does that include?
- All of them.
- Shap, glasses...
- Oh, that's Axel's too.
- Okay.
- That one too.
- Let's go.
- Come on, let's go.
- I rarely decide.
- I think we'll start with the one with the most followers.
- Okay.
- Let's start the music.
By H. R.
Put the lyrics in, grab it, you don't need to say a word
Oh, if it's something that crosses the distance I can't do it like this
If there's one thing I want to show you in my dreams
So dazzling, so bright, so shiny
Make more space for you
Stevie for you
Daisho and Jayu are so good!
Kayu I can dance with you
Miyachika Sakuma maneira
Watanabe сред久
SAKUYAMA
Sakuma "Sei" Dan "Gigi" Saku, everyone
I can dance with you
Watanabe ≪Tei Danbetsu ∑Teii Sakuma
CompositionComposition
Taisho
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ryuto Hashimoto
Ah!
Ah, ah!
A work of art.
Takahashi
Lauder
Creation and Dancing
Tanada
Inoue
Koukichi
work
Oh, it's so difficult, isn't it?
I understand.
Yes!
Here it is!
Mermaids.
You'll see.
You've got to be kidding me!
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Why is that?
Mermaid?
Why not?
Mermaids... mermaids are a different story.
You mean a real mermaid?
Real mermaids.
Don't look at me like I'm a real mermaid.
Shall we?
Here you go.
Don't waste this. You're gonna need it.
Thank you.
I'm the one who brought it out, but you don't have to take care of it.
It'll be yours in a minute.
It's so heavy.
There are mermaids, right?
No, there are definitely mermaids.
I'm sure there are mermaids.
Of course there's mermaids.
They're just out there.
But we're from the ocean.
The ocean is only, you know... 3 percent...
That's right.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
So they're definitely out there.
Oh, my God.
97% of them haven't been found yet.
That's why they're there.
They're definitely here.
Yes, I'm sure.
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes. Yes.
Nessie.
All right, all right, all right.
Let's just get this over with.
I'll finish this.
She can't finish today.
All right, we're clear.
We're gonna change it up one piece at a time.
Let's go clear.
Let's do one real change.
It's just me, right?
Then it'll look like the mermaid from earlier was joking.
I'm kidding.
The mermaid is kidding.
She said it was a joke.
That was a joke.
Okay, bye.
Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
The Palace of the Dragon King
It's over.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I think that's the best I'm gonna do on the mike today.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Suddenly it's good.
How's it going?
Let's do it.
Start the music.
It's so good. It's so good.
I wanted to go in front of it.
Come here!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Oh, oh, oh, don't let go of me
If there was magic, it wouldn't be this big
I don't need anything I don't need anything
I just want one thing
♪ It's so bright and shiny
I can see itI can see it.
I can see.
Kuroda-san, you ran.
Who's that?
It's you, after all.
What's the basic rule?
It's you.
You...
It rains a lot.
You don't know that.
I've had dinner with people other than you.
Once.
A bonus.
Of course.
-You pulled my tooth.
Amorous.
singo
Same here.
Mukai: "You guys like ramen too much?
Miyachika: "No, I..." Shichigomikake: "Let's go to Fukun Ramen!
Mukai: "Let's go to Fukun Ramen! Miyachika: "Let's go to Fufukun Ramen!
Miyachika: "Let's go to Fufun Ramen!
Miyachika: "I'm going to go after that.
Shichigosangake: "Are you going to Kenpolis?
Miyachika: "No, I'm going there, I'm talking about inside Buddy's." Sh753kake: "You're going there, I'm going there.
753: "Thermometer...let's do it!
753: "It doesn't even apply to people!" Yoshizawa: "That's the way of the times.
Yoshizawa: "Is that what the times are like? Shichigosangake: "That kind of thing... with Domoo...
Shichigosangake: "How much do you like Koban? something like that.
Miyachika: "Oh, let's do that! Let's go there! I'm thrilled...
Shichigosangake: "What do you mean by 'thrilling'? Miyachika: "Thrilling..." Yoshizawa: "No, it's not thrilling...
Yoshizawa: "No, there's someone I'm thrilled to meet.
Shichigosangake: "No, no, no, no, no..." Yoshizawa: "That's why it's so fast, isn't it?
Shichigosangake: "But you won't do it, will you? If I do that, will they know? Because they'll know.
Shichigosangake: "Before that..." Yoshizawa: "Oh, you're really going to do that?
Shichigosangake: "How excited do you think I'll be about Coban? Yoshizawa: "Koban..." Yoshizawa: "Koban..." Shichigomikake: "Koban...
Shichigosangake: "Koban? Miyachika? Yoshizawa: "Koban de...
Miyachika: "Start! Shichigosangake: "Charreen in Otogi...
Yoshizawa: "Let's go to the heart of excitement! Shichigosangake: "Charleen!
Shichigosangake: "This way! Come here!
Yoshizawa: "What, Tokimek..." Shichigosangake: "Are you sure?
Yoshizawa: "Oh, are you sure you can hear this?
Yoshizawa: "Oh, it's Coban! Shichigomikake: "What?
Yoshizawa: "At this distance..." Shichigomikake: "No!
Shichigosamikake: "Amazing, isn't it! Miyachika: "You too, you too..." Yoshizawa: "What?
Yoshizawa: "This is difficult..." Shichigozakake: "No, no, no, no..." Shichigozakake: "This is not good..." Yoshizawa: "This is not good.
Shichi-Gozan: "This is difficult. Miyachika: "Wait, wait, wait, Matsukura.
Miyachika: "Well, you came to my grandma's house, right?
Miyachika: "Well, you came to my grandma's house..." Yoshizawa: "Wow!
Yoshizawa: "At his grandma's house..." Matsukura: "Please come with me for a while..." Matsukura: "Yes, but...
Matsukura: "Well, I'm going to sleep..." Miyachika: "Oh, I heard this is real?
Miyachika: "No, I told you it's real. Yoshizawa: "Wow!
Yoshizawa: "Wow, it's amazing..." Matsukura: "You know, the "koban" story, the "koban" story...
Yoshizawa: "That's a long story!
Yoshizawa: "You're..." Matsukura: "Mmm-hmm...
Yoshizawa: "Go, go, go! Yoshizawa's passage! Matsukura: "Yes!
Matsukura: "Oh no, maybe one more time..." Yoshizawa: "Last ramen!
Yoshizawa: "Last ramen! Matsukura: "Last ramen!
Matsukura: "Last ramen! Yoshizawa: "What, last ramen?
Matsukura: "Well, I'll have a ramen now...
Yoshizawa: "This, this 20 ramen...
Yoshizawa: "How much of my feelings are in these 20 ramen...
Matsukura: "But you know what, you guys are hungry or not hungry..." Yoshizawa: "Yes, that's why...
Yoshizawa: "Yes, so let's decide based on the current situation.
Yoshizawa: "So, let's clear it up and get together.
Yoshizawa: "Let's get together with good ramen.
Yoshizawa: "Let's go!
Matsukura: "But why don't we have the last one?
Yoshizawa: "Why? Matsukura: "Don't you want to eat it? You don't want to eat it.
Yoshizawa: "I'm full... Matsukura: "I'm full... Matsukura: "Oh, that's right
Yoshizawa: "Last one!
Yoshizawa: "Let's have fun!
Yoshizawa: "Magic!
Let's go together!
LOL!
So, shall we start with those who are older than the age of youth?
Who's older?
Or the youngest?
I think I'll go with the youngest.
Low is good.
So you want to go with the childish ones?
She's in her prime.
Low.
I'll go in and out of your voice, and the words won't go away.
Oh, if there was magic in the air, I'd pretend it's gone
There's nothing I can't get 'cause you can't see me
I can't see the sky that's so bright
I can't see the sky so bright
If it's someone like Reina, it's not so close, is it? I don't know.
I see a lot of Ms. Konno, and I see Reia, maybe all the way to the end.
Isn't Reia about 5 meters away?
I thought she'd be next.
No, she's shorter than me.
Then reverse it.
You're shorter than me.
I'll, uh, I'll put in the Genmais.
I have some work to do.
Okay, here's your lunch.
Let's see who's first.
Okay! You're the first to know!Ok! I know best!
I only know the best.
Start the music!
Ha-ha-ha.
Okay.
I'll do this without a miracle.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, black!
Black!
Come a little... the word is not so hard to get.
Excuse me, sir.
These days are slippery.
If I had a back, I'd do it like that
If there's nothing I can say
I'll give you one thing
Think about it.
Oh.
I don't know.
Maybe it's me. Maybe it's a lucky guess.
I guess I'm between the two of you.
I don't know.
What?
Well, I don't remember.
I remember.
I don't remember the order.
Also, after it was over, there was a YouTube video.
What? Which one?
YouTube was on.
Almost in that order, right?
Yes, I remember.
We'll start with the ones you remember.
The first one who remembers.
Please.
Let's start.
Let's go.
What?
You, sit down.
Good morning. The person who took this picture is always a big help to me.
Yota-san, please.
Oh! It's a video or something.
Yes, it is.
Because I can't.
If it's something you can't get.
With one.
To the swing like this.
From
Like this
Shining so brightly
I'm glad.
It's a little different, though.
The sound is different.
To the shaking.
Shining.
It was good.
The sound is different, though.
The sound is different.
Though the sound is different.
Signature play
Shake.
Eh?
Oh, no.
Shake, shake, shake.
I'm in the wrong order.
Shake.
Shine.
Shine
Here.
Hands up.
No, not covered.
To the swing
Shine on.
Next.
To the shaking
Ahhh.
Oh, no.
It's me.
No thanks.
Then you're seriously different, Teddy.
There were three of us at the end.
We were the last.
We were dancing, right?
No, but we were connected.
I don't remember now.
Wow!
I didn't answer.
Wow.
Which one is it?
It's good, right?
I think it'll work.
I've been working on it my whole life.
Me!
You didn't do it?
I did.
I haven't done it in a lifetime.
Maury will be the last one or something.
I see, that DJ guy.
That's right.Yes, I do.
Big feet.
Oh, wait a minute.
Can you give me a little bit of time?
Reinia: "Come here a little, ask my hand, no need for words.
Reinia: "Another one."
Reinen: "If there was a way to bridge the distance," Reinen: "Yes, come out behind the steer, this one."
Reinen: "So what?"
Reina: "If you don't need anything, just one thing
Reina: "Because it shines so brightly" Rinnei: "No, it's embarrassing!
Rinnei: "I'm sorry, I'm sorry!"
Reina: "Okay, okay!"
RinNing: "If you knew my chi, what would you say?"
RinNing: "Thanks to you, if my heart stops, let me hear your wish." RinNing: "Okay!
RinNing: "Oh my god!"
RinNing: "I don't know which one of you is more professional!"
RinNing: "I was a singer, a singer, a singer..."
Rinnei: "I got it!"
Ling'er: "Wow! Rinnei: "There!
Rinnei: "I'm about to see the last land specs with the land specs that go through time with every crisp and silent click!
Rinnei: "Magic specs! They're magic!
Rinnei: "Wow!
Rinne: "Ha-ha-ha-ha!"
Rinnei: "I did it!
RinNing: "I did it!" Ling'er: "Not at all!"
Rinnei: "This year's fortune is good!"
Rinnei: "I know, I know, I know!"
Yahana: "Shuma-san, did you think that last time Shuma-san would come out of first place?"
Reinen: "Yes!
Reina: "Wow! Reina: "Wow!
Reina: "From the first place!
BGM
As I thought...
Always
Cute
Watanabe, you're too good to be true
sprinkler
Sakuma Oh, no!
Fukazawa, watch out! It's okay!
Sakuma, you can go!
Sakuma, just...
Yes, sir.
Yay.
Yeah!
You can't do it.
I don't know.
Eat the lyrics.
Next time, just answer it
Ready, go!
ah!
ah ah ah ah ah ah
Kemin.
Just because you were called first doesn't mean...
okay?
I see.
Suddenly Kemin
Number 10 is 1,000.
Congratulations.
What's that? No?
No. 10.
7th place is Paph. 9th place.
And that's him in 10th place.
Or even 1000th.
Eighth place.
Eighth is ninth.
That's great, but you thought we'd be ninth.
I'm eighth, which is good, because it's one place up.
That's great.
Congratulations.
That's very kind of you.
It's a head switch.
I thought you said it was turned off.
I wonder where the Halky switch is for you.
I'll find it for you.
I'll find it for you
Your very own halky switch
I got it!
Yay!
I'll know it when I see it
Buddy Claw's
When you first come in and get your 10 seats
When you get the first 10 seats
Tokyo and Osaka patterns
Which one is the best?
Let's go with the first pattern.
The one in Tokyo
Noon, isn't it?
The one in the daytime
The first show.
From the front of it.
You're at the front of the line.
I was a little scared for a moment.
There's always a word.
I don't think so.
It's over, isn't it?
Shake your head.
I can't.
I can't.I can't do it.
Who?
You.
I'm gonna have to pull it out.
I have to pull it out.
Pull him out!
Shall we go to the second show?
Halky said...
I want to do it the other way around.
You want to try?
Maybe.
Which way do you want to do it?
Behind noon.
Oh, my God.
I really don't know.
Okay, here we go.
Let's start the music.
Come here.
Hold my hand
Words are always...
I don't have words.
What?
Boo-boo.
That's the last one.
What? I thought it was night.
Oh, Shirokoi, Shirokoi.
Oh, wait, I seriously thought it was night.
Oh, no, no, no, I really thought it was night.
I really thought it was night.
I'm sorry, I'm serious.
White Castle...
I really thought it was night.
At night at the castle.
From Mr. Kasuga
Oh, Mr. Kasuga
Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Come here.
You don't need to say anything important.
Let's go this distance.
Blue.
If there was magic, we couldn't do it like that.
No, it's better this way.
Into this chest
I can't fly away
It's so dazzling
It's so bright
Baby I want you
I can't live without you
When I come to my senses
Whoa! I've got it! Soon, soon, soon
Somewhere along the way, we'll become one.
Whisper it, whisper it, whisper it, whisper it
It's the lastie bar of my heart.
Oh, my God!
Yeah!
Whoo!
It's over!
Thank you, Kasuga-san!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry I took a nap by mistake.
I made a huge mistake.
Do it now.
Let's just get it over with.
Let's just call it a night.
What's the next trick?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's do it.
Fans like it.
I don't want to do it on my own.
Me too.
They love it.
How many years of mental training did you have at the end of your career?
In the whole body,
Peter and - and the big beaters..,
You missed nothing.
I'm here for the next Fumik.
So, that's it,
Thank you again for today.
Hahahahaha
Thank you very much.
Everyone, look forward to the next one!
Listen to a lot of magic!
Please do!
I love singing out!